Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- NBC Corporate – U.S. Government
  - U.S. Government – Congress
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1973 (January-March) (Box 115, Folder 7.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1973 (March) (Box 115, Folder 8.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1973 (June-September) (Box 115, Folder 9.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1973 (September-December) (Box 115, Folder 10.)
    - House of Representatives, 1973 (February-August) (Box 115, Folder 11.)
  - U.S. Government – Congress
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1973 (January-April) (Box 116, Folder 1.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1973 (April-September) (Box 116, Folder 2.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1973 (October – December) (Box 116, Folder 3.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1974 (February 5 – March 19) (Box 116, Folder 4.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1974 (March 20-June 13) (Box 116, Folder 5.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1974 (August 12-November 1) (Box 116, Folder 6.)
    - Senate – Pastore Subcommittee – Correspondence, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 7.)
    - Senate – John Pastore – Statement, July 15, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 8.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1974 (February 11-August 8) (Box 116, Folder 9.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1974 (August 9 – December 20) (Box 116, Folder 10.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1975 (January – March) (Box 116, Folder 11.)
  - U.S. Government – Congress
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1975 (April-September) (Box 117, Folder 1.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1975 ( October-December) (Box 117, Folder 2.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1975 (April 8- November 22) (Box 117, Folder 3.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1975; Re: Fairness Doctrine (April) (Box 117, Folder 4.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1975 (January-July) (Box 117, Folder 5.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1975 (August-September) (Box 117, Folder 6.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1975; Re: Section 315 Equal Time (Box 117, Folder 7.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1975; Re: Hart Subcommittee Hearings (Box 117, Folder 8.)
    - Television Broadcasts and coverage, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 9.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1976 (January-November) (Box 117, Folder 10.)
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence – Re: Harley O. Staggers, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 11.)
    - Senate – John Pastore, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 12.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 13.)
  - U.S. Government – Congress
    - House of Representatives – Correspondence, 1977 (February-October) (Box 118, Folder 1.)
    - Senate – Correspondence, 1977; Re: Speech by JG October 22, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 2.)
  - U.S. Government – Congressional Hearings - Publications
    - Public Television Act, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 3.)
    - Political Broadcasting, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 4.)
    - Frank Stanton and CBS, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 5.)
    - Subpoenaed Material, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 6.)
    - NBC Statement Before Congress, October 3, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 7.)
  - U.S. Government – Congressional Hearings - Publications
    - Broadcast License Renewal, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 1.)
    - Broadcasting of House and Senate Proceedings, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 2.)
    - Congress and Mass Communications, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 3.)
    - Congress and Mass Communications, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 4.)
    - Violence on Television, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 5.)
  - U.S. Government – Department of Justice
    - Subpoenas to the Press, 1970 (Box 120, Folder 1.)
    - Subpoenas to the Press, 1970 (Box 120, Folder 2.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1972 (Box 120, Folder 3.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 4.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 5.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 6.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1974; Document (pg. 1-40) (Box 120, Folder 7.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1974; Document (exhibits A-D) (Box 120, Folder 8.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1974; Document (exhibits E-G, appendix A) (Box 120, Folder 9.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 10.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1975 (Box 120, Folder 11.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S. vs NBC, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 12.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S vs NBC, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 13.)
    - Anti-Trust Suit – U.S vs NBC, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 14.)
  - U.S.Government – Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - FBI (Box 121, Folder 1.)
  - U.S. Government - Federal Communications Commission
    - 1966-1967 (Box 121, Folder 2.)
    - 1968 (Box 121, Folder 3.)
    - 1969 (Box 121, Folder 4.)
    - Notice of Inquiry, 1969 (Box 121, Folder 5.)
    - 1970 (Box 121, Folder 6.)
    - Burch Speeches w/ Correspondence, 1970 (Box 121, Folder 7.)
    - Kenneth Cox; Nicholas Johnson, 1970 (Box 121, Folder 8.)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 121, Folder 9.)
    - 1974 (Box 121, Folder 10.)
    - Pensions, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 11.)
    - 1975 (Box 121, Folder 12.)
    - 1976 (1) (Box 121, Folder 13.)
    - 1976 (2) (Box 121, Folder 14.)
    - 1976 (3) (Box 121, Folder 15.)
    - 1976 (4) (Box 121, Folder 16.)
    - Commercial Television Network Practices, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 17.)
    - 1978-1989 (Box 121, Folder 18.)
    - “Fairness Doctrine” (Box 121, Folder 19.)
  - U.S. Government – General
    - 1970 (Box 122, Folder 1.)
    - 1973 (Box 122, Folder 2.)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 122, Folder 3.)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 122, Folder 4.)
    - 1975 (Box 122, Folder 5.)
    - 1976 (Box 122, Folder 6.)
  - U.S. Government – Presidential
    - Presidential Appearances, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 7.)
    - The White House, 1953-1963 (Box 122, Folder 8.)
- Gannett Corporation Board, (Materials relating to JG’s Service on the Board of Directors)
  - Gannett
    - 1979-1980 (Box 123, Folder 1.)
    - Gridiron Club, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 2.)
    - Executive Compensation Committee – 4th Quarter Report, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 3.)
    - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 4.)
    - Board of Directors, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 5.)
    - Board – USA Today Presentation, 1982; October 26, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 6.)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 7.)
    - March 5th Article on USA Today, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 8.)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Pumpkin Center, Cocoa Beach, Florida, 1983; March 22, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 9.)
    - Circulation and Compensation, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 10.)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 11.)
    - Minutes of Board Meetings and Executive Compensation, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 12.)
    - Executive Compensation Committee – Board Minutes, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 13.)
    - Correspondence and articles, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 14.)
    - USA Today, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 15.)
    - Annual Report, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 16.)
    - Correspondence and Ownership Papers, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 17.)
    - Shareholders, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 18.)
    - Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 19.)
    - Annual Report Proxy Statement, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 20.)
    - Annual Report, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 21.)
    - Executive Compensation, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 22.)
    - “The New Mexican” by Peter Katel, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 23.)
  - Gannett
    - NASA – Journalist in space, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 1.)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 2.)
    - Articles, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 3.)
    - USA Today, 1986; May 6, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 4.)
    - Third Quarter Review, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 5.)
    - Executive Incentive Bonus Recommendations, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 6.)
    - Compensation Committee, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 7.)
    - Board Meetings – Minutes (November-December), 1986 (Box 124, Folder 8.)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 124, Folder 9.)
    - Press Releases and Articles, 1987 (Box 124, Folder 10.)
    - Gannetteer (January), 1987 (Box 124, Folder 11.)
    - Board Meetings – Minutes (February – April), 1987 (Box 124, Folder 12.)
    - Board and Committee Meetings – Minutes (May –September), 1987 (Box 124, Folder 13.)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 14.)
    - Gannetteer (January, July-August), 1988 (Box 124, Folder 15.)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 16.)
    - Articles, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 17.)
    - Board of Directors – Meeting minutes, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 18.)
    - Board business, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 19.)
    - Compensation Committee, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 20.)
    - Executive Committee, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 21.)
    - USA Today, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 22.)
  - Gannett
    - Financial Statement, Period 4 – March 29, 1993-May2, 1993, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 1.)
    - Board business, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 2.)
    - Articles, 1995 (Box 125, Folder 3.)
    - Undated materials (Box 125, Folder 4.)
    - Eller, Karl (Box 125, Folder 5.)
    - Gannett. Frank E. (Box 125, Folder 6.)
    - Miller, Paul (Box 125, Folder 7.)
    - Neuharth, Allen – American Newspaper Publishers Association, April 1979 (Box 125, Folder 8.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1980-1981 (Box 125, Folder 9.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1982 (Box 125, Folder 10.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1983 (Box 125, Folder 11.)
    - Neuharth, Allen- Employment Agreement, 1983 (Box 125, Folder 12.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 13.)
    - Neuharth, Allen – Award Luncheon Center for Communication, April 5, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 14.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 15.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 16.)
    - Neuharth, Allen – The Quill, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 17.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 18.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, 1989-1991 (Box 125, Folder 19.)
    - Neuharth, Allen, Undated (Box 125, Folder 20.)
    - Quinn, John C. “The Press has Nothing to Fear but the Press Itself”, February 10, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 21.)
    - Tinker, Grant (Box 125, Folder 22.)
- Photographs
  - Official Portraits/Personal Photos
    - Official Portrait, 1950s (?) (Box 126, Folder 1.)
    - Official Portrait – early, 1960s (?) (Box 126, Folder 2.)
    - Official Portrait – early, 1960s (?) (Box 126, Folder 3.)
    - Official Portrait, April 1962 (Box 126, Folder 4.)
    - Official Portrait, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 5.)
    - Official Portrait, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 6.)
    - Official Portrait, 1968 (?) (Box 126, Folder 7.)
    - Official Portrait, December 1968 (Box 126, Folder 8.)
    - Official Portrait, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 9.)
    - Official Portrait, 1973 – 1974 (?) (Box 126, Folder 10.)
    - Official Portrait, 1973-1974 (?); Julian Goodman in his 6th floor office at Rockefeller Center (Box 126, Folder 11.)
    - Official Portrait – by Fabian Bachrach, 1977 (Box 126, Folder 12.)
    - Official Portrait, mid 1970s (?) (Box 126, Folder 13.)
    - Official Portrait (color), 1970s (?) (Box 126, Folder 14.)
    - Official Portrait (color) used in Gannett Annual Report biography, 1983 (Box 126, Folder 15.)
    - Official Portraits (negatives) – undated (Box 126, Folder 16.)
    - Julian Goodman as a young man – late, 1930s/1940s (?) (Box 126, Folder 17.)
    - Julian Goodman in NBC studio with children, 1960 (Box 126, Folder 18.)
    - Julian Goodman, 1977 (Box 126, Folder 19.)
    - Julian Goodman, 1982 (Box 126, Folder 20.)
    - Julian Goodman at Golf Course, undated (Box 126, Folder 21.)
    - Julian Goodman golfing in California – NBC Affiliates Event, 1970 (?) (Box 126, Folder 22.)
    - Julian Goodman golfing pose in his 30 Rockefeller plaza office, undated (Box 126, Folder 23.)
    - Julian Goodman at art exhibit, undated (Box 126, Folder 24.)
    - Julian Goodman at NPS Party, undated (Box 126, Folder 25.)
    - Julian Goodman at formal events, undated (Box 126, Folder 26.)
    - Post NBC retirement, 1979 (?) (Box 126, Folder 27.)
    - Family (?), undated (Box 126, Folder 28.)
    - Personal - address by Julian Goodman – undated; event unidentified (Box 126, Folder 29.)
    - Personal photos – negatives, undated (Box 126, Folder 30.)
  - People
    - Betty Goodman official portraits, undated (Box 126, Folder 31.)
    - Betty Goodman official portraits (negatives), undated (Box 126, Folder 32.)
    - Betty Goodman and Ann Brinkley at official NBC party, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 33.)
    - Betty Goodman and David Brinkley at official NBC party, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 34.)
    - Betty Goodman with Archbishop Terence-James Cooke (?) (Box 126, Folder 35.)
    - Betty Goodman and Mrs. Gerald Ford and others at reception, (undated) (Box 126, Folder 36.)
    - Betty Goodman, Julian Goodman, others unidentified, undated (Box 126, Folder 37.)
    - Betty Goodman with Julian Goodman at Gulf Oil Corporation event, undated (possibly February 5, 1970; Gulf Oil/NBC Dinner? (Box 126, Folder 38.)
    - Betty Goodman and Chet Huntley, undated (Box 126, Folder 39.)
    - Betty Goodman and unidentified woman, undated (Box 126, Folder 40.)
    - Betty and Julian Goodman, Don and Theresa Durgin, and unidentified couple (letter included), undated (Box 126, Folder 41.)
    - Adams, David with Julian Goodman at an NBC event, undated (Box 126, Folder 42.)
    - Adams, David with Julian Goodman, November 1971 (press release) (Box 126, Folder 43.)
    - Adams, Mrs. David C. (May Grelick) with Betty Goodman –undated before 1970 (Box 126, Folder 44.)
    - Arthur, William with Julian Goodman, 1972 (Box 126, Folder 45.)
    - Azcarraja, Don Emilio; Royal, John; Brunet, Meade; Goodman, Julian – Rockefeller Center, April 10, 1972 (Box 126, Folder 46.)
    - Blair, Frank with Julian Goodman, 1975 (photos inscribed to JG) (Box 126, Folder 47.)
    - Brinkley, David with Julian Goodman at Gulf oil Corporation Event, undated (possibly February 1970) (Box 126, Folder 48.)
    - Brinkley, David with Julian Goodman with letter, 1996 (Box 126, Folder 49.)
    - Brown, Governor John Y. and Phyllis George – Governor’s Development Luncheon, December 2, 1980; Pierre Hotel, New York (Box 126, Folder 50.)
    - Brown, Mrs. John Y. (Phyllis George) – Kentucky First Amendment Event with Julian Goodman (Box 126, Folder 51.)
    - Burch, Dean – Chairman (1964-74) of the FCC, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 52.)
    - Burr, Raymond (of Ironsides) and Julian Goodman, March 22, 1976; Chicago Event for ex-chairmen of NBC Affiliates Board (Box 126, Folder 53.)
    - Carson, Johnny; Julian Goodman; Don Durgin – signing NBC contract, 1966 (67?) (Box 126, Folder 54.)
    - Carson, Johnny with Julian Goodman at Gold Medal of the International Radio and Television, March 1972 (Box 126, Folder 55.)
    - Carter, President Jimmy at the White House, May 24, 1978 (Box 126, Folder 56.)
    - Chou En-Lai with Lucy Jarvis – Premier, People’s Republic of China, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 57.)
    - Cooke, Archbishop (Cardinal); Terence James with Walter Scott, Ted Walworth and Julian Goodman, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 58.)
  - Photographs – People
    - Couric, John M. with Julian Goodman, Niles Trammell and other unidentified, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 1.)
    - Cronkite, Walter with Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 2.)
    - Dorsey, B.R. President of Gulf Oil Corporation with Julian Goodman – NBC Today Show, March 25, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 3.)
    - Engstrom, Elmer (RCA President) with David Adams; Julian Goodman; William McAndrew, undated (Box 127, Folder 4.)
    - Ervin, Senator Sam – Chicago – Event for ex-chairman of NBC Affiliates Board, April 1976 (Box 127, Folder 5.)
    - Fetzer, John (owner of Detroit Tigers) with Julian Goodman and Walter Scott, undated (Box 127, Folder 6.)
    - Ford, President Gerald – Luncheon at the White House, December 18, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 7.)
    - Ford, President Gerald with Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 8.)
    - Ford, President Gerald with Julian Goodman and others, undated (Box 127, Folder 9.)
    - Ford, President Gerald with Julian Goodman and others, undated (Box 127, Folder 10.)
    - Ford, President Gerald; Mrs. Gerald Ford; Betty Goodman; Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 11.)
    - Frank, Reuven with Walter Scott and Julian Goodman at Foreign Correspondents Dinner, January 7, 1969 and other (Box 127, Folder 12.)
    - Godwin, Earl – NBC Radio Commentator, undated (Box 127, Folder 13.)
    - Goodman, Charles; Robert Goodman; Charles Goodman Jr.; Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 14.)
    - Hazam, Lou with Emmy Award (letter included), May 1962 (Box 127, Folder 15.)
    - Hope, Bob at a game, undated (Box 127, Folder 16.)
    - Humphrey, Senator Hubert with Cecil Brown; Bill McAndrew; Eric Johnston; Frederick Ford; Edwin Newman; Russell Hyde; Welles Hangen – unidentified event, undated (Box 127, Folder 17.)
    - Huntley, Chet with Julian Goodman and others at NBC Radio Affiliates Convention – New Orleans, October 1966 (Box 127, Folder 18.)
    - Huntley, Chet – Julian Goodman speaks at time of Huntley’s death, March 20, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 19.)
    - Irwin, Jim; Al Worden; Dave S. (?); Julian Goodman, November 1971 (Box 127, Folder 20.)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. at Sheraton Park Hotel – Washington, D.C., undated (Box 127, Folder 21.)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B and Mrs.; Edwin Newman; Ray Scherer; Julian Goodman – pre, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 22.)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. in Oval Office, the White House, undated (Box 127, Folder 23.)
    - Johnson, Commissioner Nicholas, January 7, 1969, Foreign Correspondents Dinner (Box 127, Folder 24.)
    - Johnston, Susan Healy (Freeman), September 12, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 25.)
    - Kennedy, Edward with Julian Goodman at the Foreign Correspondents Reception, January 1969 (Box 127, Folder 26.)
    - Kennedy, Edward; Mike Mansfield; Ernest Hollings; Edmund Muskie;Richard Wald; Julian Goodman and others at Award Presentation to Lawrence Spivak, undated (Box 127, Folder 27.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. and Mrs. Jacqueline (still from television) (Box 127, Folder 28.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Assassination and Funeral, November 1963 (Box 127, Folder 29.)
    - Kintner, Robert – transparency of painting of Robert Kinter (Box 127, Folder 30.)
    - Kintner, Robert with David Adams, David Brinkley, and Julian Goodman; Betty Goodman at official NBC event, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 31.)
    - Kissinger, Henry with Dennis Stanfill, Chairman of 20th Century Fox; Julian Goodman at NBC Affiliates Meeting – Los Angeles, 1977 (Box 127, Folder 32.)
    - Krock, Arthur with Julian Goodman, June 7, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 33.)
    - Landers, Ann (Eppie Lederer), January 1973 (Box 127, Folder 34.)
    - Lear, Norman with friend and Julian Goodman – Peabody Award, April 1977 (Box 127, Folder 35.)
    - Lemon, Bob with Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 36.)
    - Lewis, Jerry at Boy Scouts of America, undated (Box 127, Folder 37.)
    - McAndrew, William, undated (Box 127, Folder 38.)
    - McCormack, Rep. John W.; McAndrew, W.R.; Alphand, Herve – French Ambassador to the U.S.; Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 39.)
    - Meredith, Becky – WKU, May 1982 (Box 127, Folder 40.)
    - NBC Executives – Julian Goodman, David Adams, Walter Scott, Carl Lindemann, unidentified (Box 127, Folder 41.)
    - Newman, Edwin; Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 42.)
    - Newman, Edwin with French Ambassador Herve Alphand, undated (Box 127, Folder 43.)
    - Nixon, Richard M. with Walter Scott and Julian Goodman in NBC Dining Room in Rockefeller Plaza probably in 1968 (Box 127, Folder 44.)
    - Paley, William (Chairman of CBS); Herbert Schlosser, Leonard Goldenson, Julian Goodman at NBC 50th Anniversary – ?, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 45.)
    - Peppard, George – accepting award for for Banacek, October 1978 (Box 127, Folder 46.)
    - Reagan, Governor and Mrs. Ronald with Julian Goodman at WHO 50th Anniversary Luncheon, April 26, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 47.)
    - Reagan, President Ronald and Mrs. With Al Neuharth and Betty Goodman – White House address, December (?) (Box 127, Folder 48.)
    - Rockefeller, Vice President Nelson; Mrs. Rockefeller; Barbara Walters; Julian Goodman – NBC Bicentennial Party/Today Show, May 1975 (Box 127, Folder 49.)
    - Romney, George with Lawrence Spivak; Julian Goodman; Walter Scott, undated (Box 127, Folder 50.)
    - Rusk, Dean (Secretary of State, 1961-1969) with Julian Goodman and David Adams – (Box 127, Folder 51.)
    - Sarnoff, David with Julian Goodman, undated (Box 127, Folder 52.)
    - Sarnoff, Robert; Julian Goodman at Mosbacher Dinner, December 8, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 53.)
    - Sarnoff, Robert; Walter Scott; Julian Goodman – Election to RCA Board, December 1. 1971 (Box 127, Folder 54.)
  - Photographs – People
    - Sarnoff, Robert; Walter Scott; Julian Goodman, undated (Box 128, Folder 1.)
    - Scherer, Ray; James Haggerty, undated (Box 128, Folder 2.)
    - Schultz, George (Treasury Secretary); Frank Jordan (NBC); Julian Goodman, January 1969; Foreign Correspondents Reception, Washington, D.C. (Box 128, Folder 3.)
    - Scott, Walter and Julian Goodman, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 4.)
    - Scott, Willard (with Betty Goodman?) undated (Box 128, Folder 5.)
    - Sharkey, Sam; Chet Hagan; Julian Goodman – election night, undated (Box 128, Folder 6.)
    - Silverman, Fred; Edgar E. Griffiths; Julian Goodman at NYC Affiliates Meeting on June 20, 1978 (Box 128, Folder 7.)
    - Skelton, Red and his wife with Julian Goodman in Rockefeller Plaza, (undated) (Box 128, Folder 8.)
    - Spivak, Lawrence with Julian Goodman, Walter Scott, David Adams, and unidentified others, undated (Box 128, Folder 9.)
    - Tebet, David with Julian Goodman, undated (Box 128, Folder 10.)
    - Tinker, Grant with his wife Mary Tyler Moore, April 1977 (Box 128, Folder 11.)
    - Walters, Barbara; Henry Kissinger; Christina Ford – Party for Today Show – Washington, D.C., 1972 (Box 128, Folder 12.)
    - Walters, Barbara and Julian Goodman, undated (Box 128, Folder 13.)
    - Warner, Senator John with Julian Goodman – NBC Event to Celebrate 25th Anniversary of Today, 1976 (?) (Box 128, Folder 14.)
    - Wedemeyer, Dee, March 1975 (Box 128, Folder 15.)
    - Werner, Mort (selected Johnny Carson for the Tonight Show) with Julian Goodman, undated (Box 128, Folder 16.)
    - Zahedi, Ardeshir (Iranian Ambassador to U.S.) with Julian Goodman; Betty Goodman, undated (Box 128, Folder 17.)
  - Photographs - Places
    - Los Angeles – Dodgers Stadium, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 18.)
    - New Orleans – Superdome/Welcome to NBC – undated - probably, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 19.)
    - New York – Rockefeller Place; Julian Goodman in his office (Box 128, Folder 20.)
    - St. Paul, Minnesota – Radio Station KTSP, undated (Box 128, Folder 21.)
    - Unidentified and undated – Great Issues Forum – January 31, 1977, Kentucky Dinner (?) (Box 128, Folder 22.)
  - Photographs - Events
    - Awards – 1961 – Sigma Delta Chi – Julian Goodman with David Brinkley, Ted Scripps, and others (Box 128, Folder 23.)
    - Awards – 1964 – All American Award of the Year- to “the Louvre” produced by Lucy Jarvis (Box 128, Folder 24.)
    - Awards – November 18, 1967 – Sigma Delta Chi – Julian Goodman elected fellow pictured with Buren H. McCormack (Box 128, Folder 25.)
    - Awards – November 19, 1970 “Kentuckian of the Year” at Kentuckians Dinner – Julian Goodman with Harold Helm, Ray Franklin, Bill Arthur, John Y. Brown III, Elvis Stahr, Lamar Speer (Box 128, Folder 26.)
    - Awards – December 1971 – Washington D.C. – Service Awards (Box 128, Folder 27.)
    - Awards – May 7, 1975 – University of Georgia,; Athens, Georgia – George Foster Peabody Award – JG with Warren Agee; Harold Niven (Box 128, Folder 28.)
    - Awards – January 9, 1976 – Foreign Policy Association Award – Julian Goodman with Tom Brokaw; Richard Valerian; Steve Delaney; Carole Simpson; Edwin Newman; Herbert Schlosser; Irving R. Levine; Garrick Utley (Box 128, Folder 29.)